So over the course of this module, we built our own basic project setup with webpack as a build tool.
Bu nedenle, bu modln ak boyunca, webpack ile kendi temel proje kurulumumuzu bir ina arac olarak oluturduk.
Now you can go into way more detail,
Artk daha fazla ayrntya girebilir,
there's a lot you can configure,
yaplandrabileceiniz ok ey var,
you can add more loaders, more plugins and fine tune everything to your needs.
daha fazla ykleyici, daha fazla eklenti ekleyebilir ve her eyi ihtiyalarnza gre ayarlayabilirsiniz.
Definitely dive into the
Kesinlikle e-kontrolne
e-check, that configuration we have for create react app, there you can have a look at the webpack config
daln, bu tepkime tepkisi yaratma uygulamasna sahip olursunuz,
they used when setting up the create react app config though it's a very elaborate and therefore
orada oluturduklar webpack konfigrasyonuna bir
complex config.
tepki verirsiniz.
This is a simpler one because I want you to understand how webpack works and what it does
Bu daha basit bir ey nk web paketinin nasl altn ve ne yaptn anlamanz
and I hope this became a bit clearer over this module. Feel feel free to adjust and fine tune this
istiyorum ve umarm bu modl zerinde biraz daha netleir. Bu yaplandrmay ayarlamak ve ince ayar
configuration and take it as a starting point for your next projects, always dive into the github pages
yapmaktan ekinmeyin ve bir sonraki projeleriniz iin bir balang noktas olarak dnn, her zaman
where you can find the documentations of the various loaders and plugins to really configure everything
ihtiyacnz olan her eyi gerekten yaplandrmak iin eitli ykleyicilerin ve eklentilerin belgelerini bulabileceiniz
as you need it.
github sayfalarna gidin.